♪When your lies and indifference♪
♪عندما تكذب ولا مبالاتك♪
♪Pierce my heart and shatter it♪
♪اخترق قلبي وحطمه♪
♪All my piety and persistence♪
♪كل تقواي ومثابرتي♪
♪Are torn apart, turning into bubbles in the air♪
♪تتمزق وتتحول إلى فقاعات في الهواء♪
♪When my fairy tale is broken by you♪
♪عندما تحطم حكايتي الخيالية بسببك♪
♪Turning into nightmares that haunt me♪
♪تتحول إلى كوابيس تطاردني♪
♪I decide to break free from your shackles♪
♪قررت أن أتحرر من قيودك♪
♪No longer swallowing the poison apple♪
♪ لم يعد يبتلع تفاحة السم ♪
♪You fed me♪
♪لقد أطعمتني♪
♪I burn the fairy tale, rewrite the role♪
♪أحرق الحكاية الخيالية، وأعيد كتابة الدور♪
♪Reborn as a resolute me♪
♪ولدت من جديد كشخصية حازمة♪
♪I have broken free from your shackles♪
♪لقد تحررت من قيودك♪
♪Throwing away that poison apple♪
♪رمي تلك التفاحة المسمومة♪
♪You fed me♪
♪لقد أطعمتني♪
[Love Conspiracy]
[مؤامرة الحب]
[Adapted from Enhenzhai's novel, Madam, No Mercy for Scum]
[مقتبس من رواية إينهينزهاي، سيدتي، لا رحمة للحثالة]
[Episode 19]
[الحلقة 19]
Mr. Ye,
السيد يي،
the board has sent word.
لقد أرسل المجلس كلمة.
They believe the group's severe losses in recent years
ويعتقدون أن الخسائر الفادحة التي تكبدتها المجموعة في السنوات الأخيرة
are tied to your decision-making.
مرتبطة باتخاذ القرارات الخاصة بك.
Go on.
إستمر.
At this year's shareholders' meeting,
في اجتماع المساهمين لهذا العام،
they intend to remove you
إنهم ينوون إزالتك
from the chairman position.
من منصب الرئيس.
How dare they?
كيف يجرؤون؟
This is rebellion!
هذه هي التمرد!
Mr. Ye, please calm down.
السيد يي، من فضلك اهدأ.
The group has set a goal
لقد حددت المجموعة هدفًا
to secure the agency rights for Drizzt.
لتأمين حقوق الوكالة لدريزت.
They said
قالوا
they want to see your performance on this project.
إنهم يريدون رؤية أدائك في هذا المشروع.
What are our chances with the Drizzt project?
ما هي فرصنا مع مشروع Drizzt؟
From what I know,
من ما أعرفه،
Ji Baijian's Zhifu Jewelry is also making a move.
وتتحرك شركة Zhifu Jewelry التابعة لـ Ji Baijian أيضًا نحو هذا الاتجاه.
That Ji Baijian again.
أن جي بيجيان مرة أخرى.
We absolutely can't let him succeed this time.
نحن لا نستطيع أن نسمح له بالنجاح هذه المرة على الإطلاق.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
If we win the bid for Drizzt,
إذا فزنا بمناقصة Drizzt،
we can proceed with a smooth IPO.
يمكننا المضي قدمًا في الطرح العام الأولي بسلاسة.
That will shut
هذا سوف يغلق
those old fossils on the board up.
تلك الحفريات القديمة على اللوحة.
Guanshu. Find a way
غوانشو. ابحث عن طريق
to get Ji Baijian's bidding plan.
للحصول على خطة عطاءات Ji Baijian.
Ji Baijian is always very cautious.
جي بايجيان حذر للغاية دائمًا.
I'm afraid it might be difficult.
أخشى أن يكون الأمر صعبًا.
Perhaps
ربما
there's someone who can help us.
هناك شخص يمكنه مساعدتنا.
Who?
من؟
Song Zhizhi.
أغنية زيزهي.
Song Zhizhi?
أغنية Zhizhi؟
She would help us?
هل ستساعدنا؟
Last time we ruined things for her.
في المرة الأخيرة أفسدنا عليها الأمور.
She doesn't like us very much.
إنها لا تحبنا كثيرا.
Of course she doesn't.
بالطبع لا.
But right now,
ولكن في الوقت الراهن،
her father's company has been hollowed out,
لقد تم إفراغ شركة والدها ،
and she was deceived.
وقد خدعت.
She's caught between love and hatred.
لقد وقعت بين الحب والكراهية.
She's a rich girl.
إنها فتاة غنية.
What she hates most is being made a fool of.
ما تكرهه أكثر هو أن يتم جعلها أحمق.
If you hand her a knife right now,
إذا سلمتها سكينًا الآن،
she'd be only too grateful.
ستكون ممتنة للغاية.
Zhizhi, you're still working?
زيزي، هل مازلت تعمل؟
What brings you here?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
Back in the day, Starlight Jewelry was full of talent.
في الماضي، كانت Starlight Jewelry مليئة بالمواهب.
Look how quiet it is now.
انظر كم هو هادئ الآن.
You're basically manning the ship all by yourself now, huh?
أنت الآن تتولى إدارة السفينة بمفردك، أليس كذلك؟
Times have changed.
لقد تغيرت الأوقات.
Mr. Ye,
السيد يي،
if you're here to mock me,
إذا كنت هنا للسخرية مني،
you can leave now.
يمكنك المغادرة الآن.
What kind of talk is that?
ما هذا الكلام؟
I'd never mock you.
لن أسخر منك أبدًا.
You're still mad at me, aren't you?
مازلت غاضبا مني، أليس كذلك؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Let me give you a sincere apology.
دعني أقدم لك اعتذارًا صادقًا.
Let's not let this misunderstanding get worse.
دعونا لا ندع هذا سوء الفهم يزداد سوءا.
I was just trying to do you a favor and remind you
كنت أحاول فقط أن أقدم لك معروفًا وأذكرك
to watch out for Ji Baijian and his father.
لمراقبة جي بايجيان ووالده.
I never expected...
لم أتوقع أبدًا...
I didn't expect to ruin her marriage.
لم أتوقع أن أفسد زواجها.
But speaking of which,
ولكن بالحديث عن ذلك،
I actually think she and Baijian
أعتقد أنها وبيجيان فعلا
make a great couple. Right?
يشكلان ثنائيًا رائعًا. أليس كذلك؟
Mr. Ye.
السيد يي.
There's no need for this.
ليس هناك حاجة لهذا.
Oh, look at you.
أوه، أنظر إليك.
I've apologized.
لقد اعتذرت.
Why are you still being so distant?
لماذا لا تزال بعيدا جدا؟
Kid, let me tell you,
يا فتى، دعني أخبرك،
the business world is a battlefield.
عالم الأعمال هو ساحة معركة.
If you're not careful in judging people or handling matters,
إذا لم تكن حذرًا في الحكم على الأشخاص أو التعامل مع الأمور،
you can easily fall into a trap.
يمكنك الوقوع في الفخ بسهولة.
I couldn't bear to just watch you fall into a trap!
لا أستطيع أن أتحمل مجرد مشاهدتك تقع في الفخ!
You came to see me
لقد أتيت لرؤيتي
for a reason, didn't you?
لسبب ما، أليس كذلك؟
Stop beating around the bush.
توقف عن الضرب حول الشجرة.
Get straight to the point.
اذهب مباشرة إلى النقطة.
See?
يرى؟
Zhizhi's so perceptive.
Zhizhi مدرك للغاية.
Let's get down to business.
دعونا ننتقل إلى العمل.
I'll be blunt then.
سأكون صريحا إذن.
The group is preparing to bid
المجموعة تستعد لتقديم عرض
for the Drizzt agency rights project.
لمشروع حقوق وكالة Drizzt.
You know
أنت تعرف
how crucial this bid is for the group.
مدى أهمية هذا العرض بالنسبة للمجموعة.
But I've heard
ولكنني سمعت
that Ji Baijian seems to be involved as well.
ويبدو أن جي بايجيان متورط أيضًا.
Jihong Group
مجموعة جيهونج
has always been Starlight Group's
لقد كانت دائمًا مجموعة ستارلايت
most formidable competitor.
المنافس الأكثر قوة.
So
لذا
I'd like to ask for your help.
أريد أن أطلب مساعدتكم.
See if you can get their
انظر إذا كان بإمكانك الحصول عليها
bidding plan.
خطة العطاءات.
Knowing the enemy gives us a greater chance of victory.
معرفة العدو تعطينا فرصة أكبر للنصر.
Isn't that right?
أليس هذا صحيحا؟
Mr. Ye,
السيد يي،
what makes you so sure I'll help you?
ما الذي يجعلك متأكدًا من أنني سأساعدك؟
Because
لأن
I have something you want.
عندي شيء تريده.
That confident?
هل أنت واثق من ذلك؟
Say it.
قلها.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
Since you're being direct,
بما أنك مباشر،
I won't beat around the bush.
لن أطيل الحديث.
I want the list of renowned
أريد قائمة المشاهير
ancient gold crafting artisans in the country,
حرفيو صناعة الذهب القدماء في البلاد،
and the list of raw jewelry material suppliers.
وقائمة موردي المواد الخام للمجوهرات.
Zhizhi, you're asking for a lot.
زيزي، أنت تطلب الكثير.
Compared to securing the agency rights for Drizzt,
بالمقارنة مع تأمين حقوق الوكالة لدريزت،
it's not that much, is it?
إنه ليس كثيرًا، أليس كذلك؟
Besides, if Starlight Jewelry is to be rebuilt
بالإضافة إلى ذلك، إذا كان من المقرر إعادة بناء مجوهرات ستارلايت
and compete with Zhifu Jewelry,
والتنافس مع مجوهرات Zhifu،
wouldn't that only work in your favor?
ألا سيكون هذا في صالحك فقط؟
But I know Ji Baijian
لكني أعرف جي بيجيان
quite well.
جيد جدًا.
He's meticulous and cautious.
إنه دقيق وحذر.
Getting that plan
الحصول على تلك الخطة
might not be so simple.
ربما لا يكون الأمر بهذه البساطة.
I'll need time.
سأحتاج إلى الوقت.
Zhizhi,
تشيزي،
some things
بعض الأشياء
are more complicated than you think.
أكثر تعقيدًا مما تعتقد.
Starlight Jewelry has been hollowed out by the Ji family.
لقد تم تفريغ مجوهرات ستارلايت من قبل عائلة جي.
Its operations
عملياتها
are in shambles.
في حالة من الفوضى.
Rebuilding it is easier said than done.
إن إعادة بنائه أسهل قولاً من الفعل.
Mr. Ye,
السيد يي،
if I recall correctly,
إذا كنت أتذكر بشكل صحيح،
you came here to ask for my help.
لقد أتيت إلى هنا لطلب مساعدتي.
If you don't think I'm capable,
إذا كنت لا تعتقد أنني قادر،
then you should just leave.
إذن عليك أن تغادر.
Look at you.
أنظر إليك.
Always so blunt,
دائما صريحة جدا،
forgetting your place.
نسيان مكانك
If I didn't think you were capable,
إذا لم أكن أعتقد أنك قادر،
I wouldn't be here.
لن أكون هنا.
Help me get the plan,
ساعدني في الحصول على الخطة،
and I promise we'll work together
وأعدكم بأننا سنعمل معًا
to rebuild Starlight Jewelry.
لإعادة بناء مجوهرات ستارلايت.
I'll be waiting for your good news.
سأنتظر أخبارك الجيدة.
We're leaving.
نحن نغادر.
This kid is something else. Let's go.
هذا الطفل مختلف تمامًا. هيا بنا.
Guanshu.
غوانشو.
Say what you will about Zhizhi,
قل ما تريد عن Zhizhi،
but she always thinks of her father's interests.
لكنها تفكر دائمًا في مصلحة والدها.
That's the benefit of having children.
هذه هي فائدة وجود الأطفال.
Not like me,
ليس مثلي
fighting the old generation, then the young.
محاربة الجيل القديم، ثم الشباب.
Ended up all alone.
إنتهى الأمر بمفردي.
Mr. Ye, I will always be your right-hand man.
السيد يي، سوف أكون دائمًا يدك اليمنى.
Guanshu, go to the garage and wait for me with the car.
جوانشو، اذهب إلى المرآب وانتظرني بالسيارة.
I'll be right down.
سوف أكون هنا في الحال.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Come on, spill it. What's happening?
هيا، اسكبها. ماذا يحدث؟
Sir, after searching for over 20 years,
سيدي، بعد البحث لأكثر من 20 عامًا،
we finally have a lead on Da.
لدينا أخيرا دليل على دا.
She talked?
هل تحدثت؟
Yes. She said Da is still alive.
نعم، قالت أن دا لا يزال على قيد الحياة.
I'll verify it as soon as I can.
سأتحقق من ذلك في أقرب وقت ممكن.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Once confirmed, she's no longer needed.
بمجرد تأكيدها، لم تعد هناك حاجة إليها.
She knows too much.
إنها تعرف الكثير.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Mr. Ji, about that batch of rough gemstones
السيد جي، بخصوص تلك الدفعة من الأحجار الكريمة الخام
for Dafu Jewelry
لمجوهرات دافو
you asked about last time,
لقد سألت عن المرة الماضية،
I've got some new leads.
لقد حصلت على بعض الخيوط الجديدة.
I've sent you an email.
لقد أرسلت لك بريدًا إلكترونيًا.
Take a look.
خذ نظرة.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
What are these photos?
ما هذه الصور؟
We take photos of all materials during inventory check-in
نقوم بالتقاط صور لجميع المواد أثناء فحص المخزون
and check-out.
والخروج.
After your visit,
بعد زيارتك،
I still couldn't find any information on who picked up those gemstones.
لم أتمكن بعد من العثور على أي معلومات حول من التقط تلك الأحجار الكريمة.
But a couple of days ago,
ولكن قبل يومين،
while I was organizing the archives,
بينما كنت أقوم بتنظيم الأرشيف،
I found these photos
لقد وجدت هذه الصور
from that batch.
من تلك الدفعة.
When taking photos of a crate of rough gemstones being shipped out,
عند التقاط صور لصندوق من الأحجار الكريمة الخام أثناء شحنها،
we seem to have accidentally
يبدو أننا فعلنا ذلك عن طريق الخطأ
captured the person who picked them up.
تم القبض على الشخص الذي التقطهم.
Are you saying the person in this photo
هل تقول الشخص الموجود في هذه الصورة
is the one who took the gemstones?
من هو الذي أخذ الأحجار الكريمة؟
That's correct, Mr. Ji.
هذا صحيح، السيد جي.
I don't know who he is.
لا اعرف من هو.
I sent them to you.
لقد أرسلتهم إليك.
Hope it helps.
آمل أن يساعد ذلك.
Alright, thank you.
حسنًا، شكرًا لك.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Zhizhi, where are you?
تشيزهي، أين أنت؟
Haven't I made myself clear?
ألم أوضح نفسي؟
Stop bothering me.
توقف عن إزعاجي.
I've found out the truth about the rough gemstones.
لقد اكتشفت الحقيقة بشأن الأحجار الكريمة الخام.
And it concerns your dad.
ويتعلق الأمر بوالدك.
So, can I come see you?
إذن هل يمكنني أن آتي لرؤيتك؟
I'm at the office.
انا في المكتب.
Alright, I'm on my way.
حسنًا، أنا في طريقي.
Ji Baijian,
جي بيجيان,
I'm only seeing you because of my dad.
أنا أراك فقط بسبب والدي.
I believe he would never
أعتقد أنه لن يفعل ذلك أبدًا
do anything so heinous.
افعل أي شيء شنيع.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
How have you been?
كيف كان حالك؟
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
I've found out the truth about the rough gemstones.
لقد اكتشفت الحقيقة بشأن الأحجار الكريمة الخام.
My trip to Italy
رحلتي إلى إيطاليا
was to investigate the pickup order.
كان للتحقيق في أمر الاستلام.
But there was no signature on it.
ولكن لم يكن هناك توقيع عليه.
So you just assumed it was my dad?
هل افترضت للتو أنه والدي؟
It wasn't me suspecting him.
لم أكن أشك فيه.
My dad believed
كان والدي يعتقد
that since the gemstones ended up in your warehouse,
بما أن الأحجار الكريمة وصلت إلى مستودعك،
your dad must have been involved.
لا بد أن والدك كان متورطًا.
I found the person who picked those gemstones up.
لقد وجدت الشخص الذي التقط تلك الأحجار الكريمة.
It's Qian Guanshu in the photo.
إنه Qian Guanshu في الصورة.
So it must have something to do with Ye Taiting.
لذا لا بد أن يكون لهذا الأمر علاقة بـ Ye Taiting.
So it really is Ye Taiting.
لذا فهو في الحقيقة يي تايتينغ.
He framed my dad,
لقد أوقع والدي في الفخ.
which led to all that harm.
مما أدى إلى كل هذا الضرر.
Including your mother's passing.
بما في ذلك وفاة والدتك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I'm sorry, Zhizhi.
أنا آسف، زيزي.
I owe your dad an apology too.
أنا مدين لوالدك بالاعتذار أيضًا.
I never wanted to see Starlight Jewelry
لم أكن أرغب في رؤية مجوهرات ستارلايت أبدًا
end up like this.
ينتهي الأمر مثل هذا.
Losing you
فقدانك
is such a harsh punishment for me.
إنه عقاب قاسي جدًا بالنسبة لي.
Can you just give me a...?
هل يمكنك أن تعطيني فقط...؟
Stop.
قف.
You should go now.
ينبغي عليك أن تذهب الآن.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
[Ji Baijian has come to see Song Zhizhi.]
[جاء جي بيجيان لرؤية Song Zhizhi.]
[Sent]
[مرسل]
Mr. Ye.
السيد يي.
Look.
ينظر.
Good.
جيد.
Keep a close watch on them.
راقبهم عن كثب.
[Yi Wenhan]
[يي وينهان]
Wenhan.
ونهان.
You think I can't find you
هل تعتقد أنني لا أستطيع العثور عليك؟
just because you're hiding from me?
فقط لأنك تختبئ مني؟
Wenhan,
ونهان،
I'm your dad.
انا والدك
I'm not going to hide from you or abandon you.
لن أخفي عنك أو أتخلى عنك.
Dad?
أب؟
You've manipulated me with emotional lies for years.
لقد تلاعبت بي بالأكاذيب العاطفية لسنوات.
You think I still believe you?
هل تعتقد أنني لا أزال أصدقك؟
When will I get the money and see my mom?
متى سأحصل على المال وأرى أمي؟
Wenhan,
ونهان،
that's a huge sum.
وهذا مبلغ ضخم.
I need time.
أحتاج إلى الوقت.
Fine.
بخير.
Then don't blame me for what's coming.
إذن لا تلوموني على ما سيأتي.
Let's see if Ye Taiting will still tolerate you
دعونا نرى ما إذا كان يي تايتينغ سيظل يتسامح معك
once he knows everything.
بمجرد أن يعرف كل شيء.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
Three days.
ثلاثة أيام.
You have three days.
لديك ثلاثة أيام.
I want the money, and I want to see my mom.
أريد المال، وأريد أن أرى أمي.
Then don't blame me for getting tough.
إذن لا تلومني على كوني قاسيًا.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Mr. Ji,
السيد جي،
the board members are not supportive of Zhifu Jewelry
أعضاء مجلس الإدارة لا يدعمون مجوهرات Zhifu
bidding for the Drizzt project. Should we continue?
هل نستمر في تقديم العطاءات لمشروع دريزت ؟
I know.
أنا أعرف.
I know the shareholders
أنا أعرف المساهمين
have strong opinions about the Drizzt project.
لدي آراء قوية حول مشروع Drizzt.
I'll speak with them personally.
سأتحدث معهم شخصيا.
Zhizhi.
تشيزهي.
I was just passing by and thought I'd check on you.
كنت أمر فقط وفكرت في التحقق منك.
Mr. Ye, you've been coming to me repeatedly lately.
السيد يي، لقد كنت تأتي إلي مرارا وتكرارا في الآونة الأخيرة.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
I see you're full of ambition,
أرى أنك مليء بالطموح،
pushing so hard to rebuild your father's company.
بذلت جهدًا كبيرًا لإعادة بناء شركة والدك.
I was worried you might be overworking yourself.
كنت قلقة من أنك قد تجهد نفسك بالعمل.
Just wanted to see how you're holding up.
أردت فقط أن أرى كيف حالك.
There's no need for you to worry about my work.
لا داعي للقلق بشأن عملي.
So, how is it going
إذن كيف تسير الأمور؟
with that matter I asked you about?
بخصوص هذا الأمر الذي سألتك عنه؟
So you're here to check on the progress.
لذا فأنت هنا للتحقق من التقدم.
Not exactly. Well,
ليس بالضبط. حسنًا،
we're clear-headed.
نحن ذوو رؤوس صافية.
Let me be frank with you.
دعني أكون صريحا معك.
I've enlisted others
لقد جندت الآخرين
within Zhifu Jewelry
داخل مجوهرات زيفو
to help me with this project as well.
لمساعدتي في هذا المشروع أيضًا.
So
لذا
you're not my only card to play.
أنت لست البطاقة الوحيدة التي ألعب بها.
But I can tell you for sure
ولكن يمكنني أن أخبرك بالتأكيد
that no one but Starlight Group
أن لا أحد سوى مجموعة ستارلايت
can give you
يمكن أن تعطيك
what you want.
ما تريد.
Mr. Ye.
السيد يي.
You've certainly done your homework.
لقد قمت بالتأكيد بواجبك.
You might not know.
ربما لا تعرف.
But Ji Baijian
لكن جي بيجيان
is personally overseeing this project.
يشرف شخصيا على هذا المشروع.
[Ji Baijian] [Zhizhi, I'm sorry.]
[جي بيجيان] [زهيزهي، أنا آسف.]
For a project personally overseen by Ji Baijian,
بالنسبة للمشروع الذي أشرف عليه شخصيًا جي بايجيان،
all the core secrets
كل الأسرار الأساسية
are undoubtedly in his hands.
فهي بلا شك بين يديه.
Those small fries at the company
تلك البطاطس المقلية الصغيرة في الشركة
are useless.
لا فائدة منها.
The only one of your cards
البطاقة الوحيدة من بطاقاتك
who can get that file from him
من يستطيع الحصول على هذا الملف منه؟
is me.
انا هو.
Be patient.
كن صبوراً.
I am patient.
أنا صبور.
I have plenty of patience.
لدي الكثير من الصبر.
Alright then, Zhizhi,
حسنا إذن، زيزي،
I'll let you get back to work.
سأدعك تعود إلى العمل.
See yourself out.
انظر نفسك بالخارج.
Okay. Alright.
حسناً. حسناً.
Ji Baijian,
جي بيجيان,
where are you?
أين أنت؟
I need to see you.
أريد رؤيتك.
Zhizhi,
تشيزي،
I didn't expect you to reach out.
لم أتوقع منك أن تمد يدك.
Does this mean you forgive me?
هل هذا يعني أنك تسامحني؟
Get in the car first.
ادخل إلى السيارة أولاً.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
See that car over there?
هل ترى تلك السيارة هناك؟
Are we being followed?
هل يتم متابعتنا؟
Ye Taiting's men.
رجال يي تايتينغ.
Did he do anything to you?
هل فعل لك شيئا؟
Ye Taiting came to see me.
جاء يي تايتينغ لرؤيتي.
He wanted to discuss a deal.
أراد مناقشة صفقة.
A deal?
صفقة؟
He wants me to get
يريدني أن أحصل عليه
Zhifu Jewelry's bidding plan
خطة المزايدة لشركة Zhifu Jewelry
for the Drizzt project from you.
لمشروع Drizzt منك.
So he had someone follow me
لذلك كان لديه شخص يتبعني
and keep an eye on me.
وراقبني.
In exchange, he said...
وفي المقابل قال..
Zhizhi,
تشيزي،
you know what Ye Taiting is like.
أنت تعرف ما هو Ye Taiting.
Don't let him fool you.
لا تدعه يخدعك.
If you want something,
إذا كنت تريد شيئا،
whatever Ye Taiting is offering, I can...
مهما كان ما يقدمه Ye Taiting، فأنا أستطيع...
You can't give it to me.
لا يمكنك أن تعطيه لي.
And I don't trust you anymore.
ولم أعد أثق بك بعد الآن.
But to be honest,
ولكن لكي أكون صادقا،
Ji Baijian,
جي بيجيان,
even though you lied to me,
حتى لو كذبت علي،
I don't want to harm you.
لا أريد أن أؤذيك.
So I won't steal your plan.
لذلك لن أسرق خطتك.
I came to see you
لقد جئت لرؤيتك
to propose we work together.
أن نقترح أن نعمل معًا.
Let's put on a show for him.
دعونا نقدم عرضًا له.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Thank you for telling me.
شكرا لك على إخباري.
No need to thank me.
لا داعي لشكرني.
I'm not doing this for you.
انا لا افعل هذا من اجلك .
I just don't want to compromise
أنا فقط لا أريد التنازل
my own professional ethics.
أخلاقياتي المهنية الخاصة.
I think we share a common goal
أعتقد أننا نتقاسم هدفًا مشتركًا
when it comes to
عندما يتعلق الأمر بـ
dealing with Ye Taiting.
التعامل مع Ye Taiting.
So I want you to help me get
لذلك أريدك أن تساعدني في الحصول على
what I want.
ما أريده.
What do you need me to do?
ماذا تريدني أن أفعل؟
I need you to prepare a fake bidding plan.
أريد منك إعداد خطة مزايدة وهمية.
Make it detailed.
اجعلها مفصلة.
Make Ye Taiting believe it.
اجعل يي تايتينغ يصدق ذلك.
After this is over,
بعد أن انتهى هذا،
I want to buy twenty percent of your shares
أريد شراء عشرين بالمئة من أسهمك
in Starlight Jewelry.
في مجوهرات ستارلايت.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I agree.
أنا موافق.
Let's go then.
دعنا نذهب إذن.
They're still following you.
إنهم لا زالوا يتبعونك.
Sell the lie.
بيع الكذبة
Let's go to your place.
دعنا نذهب إلى مكانك.
Have you been
هل كنت؟
having a tough time lately?
هل تواجه وقتًا عصيبًا في الآونة الأخيرة؟
Not really.
ليس حقيقيًا.
Just a lot going on recently.
لقد حدث الكثير مؤخرًا.
Is there anything I can do to help?
هل هناك أي شيء يمكنني القيام به للمساعدة؟
I don't need your help.
لا أحتاج إلى مساعدتك.
You should rest when we get home.
ينبغي عليك أن ترتاح عندما نصل إلى المنزل.
I'll make something to eat.
سأصنع شيئا للأكل.
It's late. You probably don't have time to eat.
لقد تأخر الوقت. ربما ليس لديك وقت للأكل.
You must be hungry.
لابد أنك جائع.
Thank you, Mr. Ji.
شكرا لك سيد جي.
But from now on, when it's just us,
ولكن من الآن فصاعدا، عندما يتعلق الأمر بنا فقط،
there's no need to keep up the act.
ليس هناك حاجة لمواصلة هذا الفعل.
♪We stubbornly turn our backs, putting up a front♪
♪نحن ندير ظهورنا بعناد، ونضع واجهة ♪
♪Creating this illusion of peace♪
♪خلق هذا الوهم بالسلام♪
♪Raindrops streak the car window♪
♪قطرات المطر تلطخ نافذة السيارة♪
♪Sliding down too hurriedly♪
♪الانزلاق إلى أسفل بسرعة كبيرة♪
♪Burning as they reach my heart♪
♪تحترق عندما تصل إلى قلبي♪
Have some warm water.
تناول بعض الماء الدافئ.
Just leave it there.
فقط اتركه هناك.
♪By the moon's faint light♪
♪على ضوء القمر الخافت♪
♪The room stretches endlessly, hollow and vast♪
♪تمتد الغرفة إلى ما لا نهاية، جوفاء وواسعة♪
♪This love is forced into descent♪
♪هذا الحب مُجبر على النزول♪
You don't need to fuss.
لا داعي للقلق.
♪Tears are gathered♪
♪الدموع تتجمع♪
♪By my eyes♪
♪بعيني♪
If you're too tired, get some rest.
إذا كنت متعبًا جدًا، احصل على بعض الراحة.
Don't stay up too late.
لا تسهر كثيرا.
♪They blow into the most fragile corners of my heart♪
♪إنهم ينفخون في أكثر زوايا قلبي هشاشة♪
♪Silently colliding♪
♪تصادم بصمت♪
♪I want to hold you♪
♪أريد أن أحتضنك♪
There's soup in the pot.
هناك حساء في القدر.
♪Grab onto your shoulders♪
♪أمسك بكتفيك♪
♪But I end up opening the window instead♪
♪لكنني انتهي بفتح النافذة بدلاً من ذلك♪
♪Even that goodbye remains♪
♪حتى هذا الوداع يبقى ♪
♪Remains unspoken, silent♪
♪يبقى غير مذكور، صامت♪
♪In the end, we can't even be friends♪
♪في النهاية، لا يمكننا حتى أن نكون أصدقاء♪
♪You just leave like that♪
♪لقد غادرت هكذا فقط♪
♪My story's second half♪
♪النصف الثاني من قصتي♪
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Mr. Ye,
السيد يي،
we have news about your son.
لدينا أخبار عن ابنك.
After multiple confirmations,
بعد تأكيدات متعددة،
the news is absolutely reliable.
الخبر موثوق تماما.
You'll never guess who it is.
لن تخمن أبدًا من هو.
Ziming, you've been working hard.
زيمينغ، لقد كنت تعمل بجد.
Here, let me toast you.
هنا، اسمح لي أن أشرب نخبًا لك.
Mr. Ye,
السيد يي،
what's the occasion for this dinner?
ما هي مناسبة هذا العشاء؟
I've been wanting to find time to sit down with you.
لقد كنت أريد أن أجد الوقت للجلوس معك.
Qian has spoken to you, hasn't he?
لقد تحدث إليك تشيان، أليس كذلك؟
So I wanted to take this opportunity
لذلك أردت أن أغتنم هذه الفرصة
to ask you directly.
لأسألك مباشرة.
Would you like to take a position in the group?
هل ترغب في تولي منصب في المجموعة؟
I made myself very clear to Mr. Qian.
لقد أوضحت نفسي للسيد تشيان.
I must repay
يجب علي أن أسدد
the Song family's kindness.
لطف عائلة سونغ.
I'm afraid I'll have to disappoint you, Mr. Ye.
أخشى أنني سأضطر إلى خذلانك، سيد يي.
Not at all.
مُطْلَقاً.
For a young man,
بالنسبة لشاب،
you have such a strong sense of loyalty.
لديك شعور قوي بالولاء.
I admire that.
أنا معجب بذلك.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
you're also fond of Zhizhi, aren't you?
أنت أيضًا تحب Zhizhi، أليس كذلك؟
You've been investigating me?
هل كنت تحقق معي؟
That's my personal matter.
هذه مسألة شخصية بالنسبة لي.
You're overstepping.
لقد تجاوزت الحد.
I'm afraid
انا خائف
I can't continue this meal.
لا أستطيع مواصلة هذه الوجبة.
Ziming.
زيمينج.
I know,
أنا أعرف،
as the Song family's adopted kid,
باعتباره الطفل المتبنى لعائلة سونغ،
you have some prejudices against me.
لديك بعض الأحكام المسبقة ضدي.
I totally understand.
انا أفهم تماما.
But
لكن
I still have to show you something.
لا يزال يتعين علي أن أعرض عليك شيئًا.
[DNA Paternity Test Report]
[تقرير اختبار الأبوة DNA]
[Regarding the Paternity Relationship Between Wei Ziming and Ye Taiting]
[فيما يتعلق بعلاقة الأبوة بين وي زيمينغ ويي تايتينغ]
[Probability of Paternity: 99.99%]
[احتمال الأبوة: 99.99٪]
[Intimate Relationship]
[العلاقة الحميمة]
Still reading so late?
هل لا تزال تقرأ حتى وقت متأخر؟
Are you interested in this book?
هل أنت مهتم بهذا الكتاب؟
Just trying to learn.
فقط أحاول أن أتعلم.
I've realized I simply don't understand,
لقد أدركت أنني ببساطة لا أفهم،
and don't know how to build any kind of intimate relationship.
ولا أعرف كيف أبني أي نوع من العلاقات الحميمة.
I've read this book too.
لقد قرأت هذا الكتاب أيضاً.
What were your thoughts
ما هي أفكارك
after finishing it?
بعد الانتهاء منه؟
The book says
الكتاب يقول
only by resolving your own issues
فقط من خلال حل مشاكلك الخاصة
can you do better when a new relationship
هل يمكنك أن تفعل بشكل أفضل عندما تكون في علاقة جديدة؟
comes along.
يأتي على طول.
I'm sorry, Zhizhi.
أنا آسف، زيزي.
It's because of my own personal issues
هذا بسبب مشاكلي الشخصية
that our relationship
أن علاقتنا
has ended up like this.
لقد انتهى الأمر بهذا الشكل.
This...
هذا...
What is this photo? This is...?
ما هذه الصورة؟ هذه...؟
It's my...
إنها...
My friend's.
أصدقائي.
I'll return it to him another day.
سأعيده إليه في يوم آخر.
You should get some rest.
ينبغي عليك الحصول على بعض الراحة.
Ji Baijian,
جي بيجيان,
you really are still keeping things from me.
أنت حقا لا تزال تخفي أشياء عني.
♪From this moment on, I no longer care♪
♪من هذه اللحظة فصاعدا، لم أعد أهتم♪
♪No more noise in my ears♪
♪لا مزيد من الضوضاء في أذني♪
♪That's the peace I've always yearned for♪
♪هذا هو السلام الذي كنت أشتاق إليه دائمًا♪
♪Who was I trying to change for?♪
♪من كنت أحاول التغيير من أجله؟♪
♪Smiling, crying, complaining♪
♪يبتسم، يبكي، يشكو♪
♪That's the contentment I should learn to embrace♪
♪هذا هو الرضا الذي يجب أن أتعلم احتضانه♪
♪Honestly, I don't care♪
♪ بصراحة، لا يهمني ♪
♪How many times you've hurt me♪
♪كم مرة جرحتني♪
♪What you call sincere devotion♪
♪ما تسميه التفاني الصادق♪
♪Maybe I've just grown numb♪
♪ربما أصبحت مخدرًا للتو♪
♪Honestly, I don't care♪
♪ بصراحة، لا يهمني ♪
♪Even if I've strayed♪
♪حتى لو ضللت الطريق♪
♪I'm still crying for someone♪
♪مازلت أبكي من أجل شخص ما♪
♪Crying over losing to my own pride♪
♪ البكاء على الخسارة أمام كبريائي ♪